Actually, by extension, a way to try to reduce the entire large resource consumption that is the consequences of -
- That we use things for a very long time and then replace them with something new.
It is very exciting and it would be very fun if it took off and favored in different ways in society.
There are many tests in different places among different companies and different phenomena that already exist that mean this.
But that it was scaled up and became the new norm would in some way be very, very good.
And it would also mean that climate emissions dropped dramatically as this entire resource sales -
- As we do, a lot of resources cost.
And then when we have used them, they suddenly become hopelessly mixed and we cannot benefit from them again.
Instead of using them for as long as possible and finding ways to make sure we don't have to replace everything -
- Without just replacing parts and so on.